{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "5c28e193782fde0bc8740e45" }, "userName" : "laura", "type" : "c++", "Questions" : [ { "question" : "Which of the followings is/are pointer-to-member declarator?", "solution" : "", "correct" : false }, { "question" : "Which is private member functions access scope?", "solution" : "", "correct" : false }, { "question" : " Which of these best describes an array?", "solution" : "", "correct" : false }, { "question" : "What do you call the languages that support classes but not polymorphism?", "solution" : "", "correct" : false }, { "question" : "A process can be _______?", "solution" : "", "correct" : false }, { "question" : " Generic pointers can be declared with__________ . ", "solution" : "", "correct" : false }, { "question" : "Which one of the following is not shared by threads?", "solution" : "", "correct" : false }, { "question" : " How do you initialize an array in C?", "solution" : "", "correct" : false } ], "score" : 0, "state" : false, "__v" : 0 }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "5c28e19a782fde0bc8740e47" }, "userName" : "laura", "type" : "data structure", "Questions" : [ { "question" : " What is the maximum height of an AVL tree with p nodes?", "solution" : "", "correct" : false }, { "question" : "In Breadth First Search of Graph, which of the following data structure is used?", "solution" : "", "correct" : false }, { "question" : " Which of the following applications may use a stack?", "solution" : "", "correct" : false }, { "question" : " What is an AVL tree?", "solution" : "a tree which is balanced and is a height balanced tree", "correct" : true }, { "question" : " Which of these best describes an array?", "solution" : "Container of objects of mixed types", "correct" : false }, { "question" : " How do you initialize an array in C?", "solution" : "int arr(3) = {1,2,3};", "correct" : false }, { "question" : " Process of inserting an element in stack is called ____________", "solution" : "Push", "correct" : true }, { "question" : "The data structure required for Breadth First Traversal on a graph is?", "solution" : "Queue", "correct" : true } ], "score" : 3, "state" : true, "__v" : 0 }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "5c2b25212f9ec71be8f7a5da" }, "userName" : "jan", "type" : "c++", "Questions" : [ { "question" : " Generic pointers can be declared with__________ . ", "solution" : "", "correct" : false }, { "question" : " How do you initialize an array in C?", "solution" : "", "correct" : false }, { "question" : "Which among the following best describes polymorphism?", "solution" : "", "correct" : false }, { "question" : "What do you call the languages that support classes but not polymorphism?", "solution" : "Procedure Oriented language", "correct" : false }, { "question" : "If one thread opens a file with read privileges then", "solution" : "all of the mentioned", "correct" : false }, { "question" : "Which of the followings is/are pointer-to-member declarator?", "solution" : "None of these", "correct" : false }, { "question" : "A process can be _______?", "solution" : "all of the above", "correct" : false }, { "question" : " Which of these best describes an array?", "solution" : "All of the mentioned", "correct" : false } ], "score" : 0, "state" : true, "__v" : 0 }
